https://www.afc-ca.com/privacy-cookie-policy/

Privacy & Cookie Policy | AFC Finishing Systems
(800) 331-7744 sales@afc-ca.com
Search for:
Paint SolutionsQuadraft Automotive Spray BoothXtreme Series Downflo Automotive Spray BoothsSDD Xtreme Spray BoothThermal Xtreme Spray BoothSingle Wall Downflo Automotive Spray BoothsSide Downflo Spray BoothDouble Row Downflo Spray BoothCrossflo Automotive Spray BoothsTruck Spray BoothsAuto/Truck Crossflo Spray BoothCrossflo Truck Spray BoothDouble Row Downflo Truck Spray BoothSide Downflo Truck Spray BoothIndustrial Spray BoothsIndustrial OvensIndustrial Liquid Coating ProductsAir Make-Up UnitsDFM800R/DFM2000AMS1000/AMS2000Prep StationsPrep BenchesWork StationsPaint Mixing RoomsOther ProductsOpen Front Spray BoothsDrying enclosuresBench spray boothsExhaust chambers & benchesBlast SolutionsPowder CoatingSpray BoothsOvensAccessoriesPart & FiltersTurbo Cure Air Auxiliary Movement SystemJetAir Air Auxiliary Movement SystemDoorsLight FixturesExhaust Fans & DuctworkPower Shield SystemCompanyAbout UsTestimonialsFAQsResourcesContact ContactPaint SolutionsQuadraft Automotive Spray BoothXtreme Series Downflo Automotive Spray BoothsSDD Xtreme Spray BoothThermal Xtreme Spray BoothSingle Wall Downflo Automotive Spray BoothsSide Downflo Spray BoothDouble Row Downflo Spray BoothCrossflo Automotive Spray BoothsTruck Spray BoothsAuto/Truck Crossflo Spray BoothCrossflo Truck Spray BoothDouble Row Downflo Truck Spray BoothSide Downflo Truck Spray BoothIndustrial Spray BoothsIndustrial OvensIndustrial Liquid Coating ProductsAir Make-Up UnitsDFM800R/DFM2000AMS1000/AMS2000Prep StationsPrep BenchesWork StationsPaint Mixing RoomsOther ProductsOpen Front Spray BoothsDrying enclosuresBench spray boothsExhaust chambers & benchesBlast SolutionsPowder CoatingSpray BoothsOvensAccessoriesPart & FiltersTurbo Cure Air Auxiliary Movement SystemJetAir Air Auxiliary Movement SystemDoorsLight FixturesExhaust Fans & DuctworkPower Shield SystemCompanyAbout UsTestimonialsFAQsResourcesContact
Privacy & Cookie Policy This Privacy Policy was updated on May 2nd 2018.We comply with our obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998, The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018, and the Data Protection Act that this regulation enacts. We are wholly committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and this policy explains how we collect, use, process and protect your personal information.What is personal information?
We define personal information primarily as names, telephone and mobile numbers, email addresses and property addresses. However, personal information may also include location data and online identifiers like IP addresses.What personal information do we collect from you?We collect personal information from you when you interact with us or use our services. Currently, the only information we collect from this website is what you give us when you complete a contact form, use Live Chat, or when you call us. We do not track your IP address or other personal identifying data during your visit to this website.We use cookies to help support normal website function and to monitor broad visitor data via Google Analytics. This is an anonymous system that is not able to provide us with personal identifying data.A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. This information is anonymised by Google, we only use it for statistical analysis purposes, and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.You have control over consent and can tick the relevant boxes on the Contact Us form to give your consent (or not) to continued contact. If you do not give us your consent, we do not have the right to contact you again outside the context of your original enquiry.Social MediaWhere we undertake social media advertising, it is important to be aware that some of our social media pages give us automatic access to some of your personal information that they store about you (for example, posts you have liked, adverts or content you have viewed). You control the personal information you allow us to have access to through the privacy settings on each of your applicable social media sites.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.How do we use your personal information?We use your personal information to: provide and improve our products and services, provide you with a personalised experience on our sites, contact you about your enquiry or order, provide you with personalised customer service, and provide you with personalised advertising and marketing.We may contact you to process payment, to manage your order, to measure or improve our services, to solve problems or discuss any relevant aspect of your enquiry or otherwise as necessary to provide normal customer service. We may contact you by phone, email, SMS or postal mail.We may use general location information to provide you with location based services (such as advertising and other personalised content). If we use a third party for any contractual or order fulfilment process, they will only retain and use your personal contact information for the period required to undertake this process and are bound by the rules laid out in this policy.We use your personal information to pursue our legitimate interests where your rights and freedoms do not outweigh these interests. We have implemented controls to balance our interests with your rights. Where we have your consent, this includes: contacting you via email or postal mail in order to offer you discounts and special promotions and targeted marketing, to research the effectiveness of our products and services through surveys or questionnaires, to measure the performance of our email marketing campaigns by analysing open and click rates and to inform you about our services, as authorised by applicable law.How do we process your personal information? We store your data securely using suitable systems and processes. We occasionally process your data using an external platform called Mail Chimp. This platform is used to help us send email marketing campaigns. You can find out more about your data use with Mail Chimp in their privacy policy which can be accessed here. Sections 6 and 7 of their policy deal with processing of your data, but they make clear that we hold the responsibility for your data while using this platform. If you would not like Mail Chimp to process your data for marketing, you should contact us and let us know.How can you access, manage or correct your personal information?You have the right to request access to your personal information as well as request corrections, restrictions on use or complete removal of your personal information. We will provide you with a copy of your personal information on request in Microsoft Word format and will honour any requests for amendments or removal. This right is determined by applicable law.If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can unsubscribe via the link in an email you received, indicate your communication preferences using the Contact Us page on our website, or contact us at any time by emailing info@afc-ca.com or calling: 0845 7697225.Do we share your personal information?We do not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. We will only use your personal information to process your enquiry or order and send you promotional information which we think you may find interesting if you have given us your permission to do so. We minimise the amount of personal information we disclose to our employees and partners as indicated above and then only use data that is directly relevant and necessary to accomplish the specified purpose.How long do we keep your personal information?We keep your data for as long as necessary to provide you with the information, products or services you have enquired about or for other essential purposes such as complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our policies. You can ask us to remove your data at any time by sending a request to info@afc-ca.comHow do we protect your personal information?We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Some of the safeguards we use are: firewalls, data encryption, access and authorisation controls.After it is no longer necessary for us to retain your personal information or following a personal request to remove your personal information, we will dispose of it in a secure manner.We may amend this privacy notice at any time by posting the amended version on this website. AFC Finishing Systems, 250 Airport Parkway, Oroville, CA 95965 Paint SolutionsQuadraft Automotive Spray BoothXtreme Series Downflo Automotive Spray BoothsSingle Wall Downflo Automotive Spray BoothsCrossflo Automotive Spray BoothsTruck Spray BoothsIndustrial Spray BoothsIndustrial OvensIndustrial Liquid Coating ProductsAir Make-Up UnitsPrep StationsPaint Mixing RoomsOther ProductsBlast SolutionsBlast SolutionsPowder CoatingSpray BoothsOvensAccessoriesPart & FiltersTurbo Cure Air Auxiliary Movement SystemJetAir Air Auxiliary Movement SystemDoorsLight FixturesExhaust Fans & DuctworkPower Shield SystemSocialCompanyAbout UsTestimonialsFAQsResourcesJoin our mailing list
We will never sell or share your data. You can see our Privacy Policy here.Leave this field empty if you're human:
© 2020 Copyright AFC Finishing Systems. Site by MarcusSanderson.com Contact DetailsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy & Cookie PolicySitemap This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Accept Reject Read MoreCookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary Always Enabled
